r4ds-ds.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy

R4DS-DS recognize the importance to protect the privacy and financial information of our customers. We are committed to protect your privacy interest by using different measures to maintain your trust in shopping with us. At no point shall we sell, share and trade or disclose the personal information of our customers. This privacy policy tells you what information we collect and how we use these informations. We suggest you to read this policy, before using our website or submitting any information, to know what kind of personal information we may collect from you when you are using the site. By using our site, you consent to accept the practices stated in this privacy policy.

In this private policy, the terms "we", "our" and "us" refer to R4DS-DS or R4DS-DS.com or Fr.r4ds-ds.com or It.r4ds-ds.com.

### Collection and use of information:

We collect the aggregate information (not personally indentifiable) on the general usage of the website, such as what pages are viewed most frequently by visitors and the domaine name of the visitors’ email address. This information helps us to monitor the use of the site and to improve the performance and efficiency of our website. Also, we collect information from survey responses, comments and our contact form when you are asking questions etc, at your volunteer.

To process an order, we need to collect your personally indentifiable information such as: your name, email address, telephone number, billing address, credit card number, expiration date etc. We are using these information to fulfill your order and to inform you the status or tracking information of your order. Also, we store the record of your purchase histories and your product interest. We may use all this information combined all together to improve your shopping experience, for example, to notify you occasionlly our new service or seasonal promotion event that we think you’ll be interested in.

You can also easily unsubscribe from receiveing any future email from us by following the detailed instructions of unsubscribe at the bottom of each of our email or by filling a contact form at our website to contact our customer care team.

### Cookies:

Like many other websites, we use cookies, small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive. This tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, the frequency of that certain page is visited and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can help customize the Site for visitors and enhance the online shopping experience. Please be awared that cookies will not collect any personally indentifiable information unless the information has been previously provided.

Upon visiting our site, cookies will be issed except that you have modified the setting of you browers to refuse cookies. Declining cookies will prevent you from taking full advantage of our site.

### Distribution of information:

Except as discribed in this section, we will not sell, share, trade and disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties.

In order to fulfill the shipment of your order, we make your name and mailling address availeble to such carriers like post, DHL, etc. These companies will respect customers privacy and at no point they are allowed to make any other use of these information.

Please note that we may be required to share information with governmental agencies or other third parties to comply with laws, regulations, government requests, or to protect the rights of R4DS-DS or others.

### Data security:

To protect your privacy agaist unauthorized access and improper use, we have implemented SSL(Secure sockets layer) technology in our payment gateway. While entering, the SSL technology transfers all the personal information into encrypt form before the transmission of the information. R4DS-DS promise that we will continue to enhance our security procedures in order to provide you an secure online shopping environment with our system. While we are making our best to ensure the secrurity of your information, it's still impossible to guarantee a 100% secure transmission over internet. Thus, you’re doing the transmission of information at your own risk.

### Changes to this private policy:

R4DS-DS reserve the right to modify occasionnaly the pratices of this private policy. Should any changes be made to this private policy, we will post the updated version on our site.

This private policy is last modified on may 03, 2012.

### Contact us:

Should you have any comments or queries regarding our private policy, please contact us by filling out a contact form at our site www.r4ds-ds.com, or simply email to: [sales@r4ds-ds.com](mailto:sales@r4ds-ds.com).
